Ajay has this
Hello guys today we are going to learn how to
apply for free and post
hospitalization Friends, before this I
applied for main hospitalization, I
mean I have made a complete video on how to
apply for it and after that I was getting a lot of
comments that sir you should
make a video on pre and post graduation as well, for that friends
I have made a video today, so today we are going to
see what pre and post graduation is,
Prince Pistol Hospitalization
means the opposite of our main
hospitalization which is timingless, the
first
30 day period of main hospitalization is
called free hospitalization, this is the
process of hospitalization, after
consulting a doctor, whatever
medicines we take, whatever tests we get done
and whatever expenses we incur in the hospital,
whatever
explanation we have to give for it, we call it Prince
Fertilization Apps,
after that friends
I would like to tell you about post hospitalization,
if we have to apply for the process of post hospitalization, then
after our main hospitalization, our
discharge will be done  Next 16th of the pictures, we
can add post hospitalization, whatever our bills are, whatever
reports of our tests etc.,
whatever our receipts are,
we can apply those papers in post hospitalization
and we have been given a time limit of up
to 6 days for it. ICICI
Lombard has 30 days free
and 6 days after post graduation, so whatever we have
spent three days before hospitalization,
we can call it free hospitalization express
and
whatever we will have to spend for 7 days after side hospitalization,
we will call it post hospitalization
express, so
what do we have to do here,
which documents do we have to
submit here on time, friends, miss,
I have made a video before this,
I have
explained the entire process for specialization in it, if you people have
seen it in the video, then
I have given it in the description box,
you can go and check that video
and from there you can see how we  Those who
apply have to do it and which
documents will have to be submitted here, so
friends, during that time, whatever
visits etc. we had, whatever
tests we had done, the
company will bear all the expenses of all of them
till 360 days in post hospitalization
and after that, friends,
many people had commented to me
that my cashless process has been done,
whatever was my main hospitalization bill,
friends, whatever was the main
hospitalization bill during admission, whatever would have been the
cost of that, then it is one of the
best processes for such people, friends, I liked it,
cashless, so if many
people have done cashless
during hospitalization, then I also got comments about how to apply for them pre and post,
so today I am going to tell you
that if we have done cashless process
or we have applied for re-investment, then
we can apply for that too, friends, if you have time then it is for
30 days and studies
We have to apply it in it
and after liking it, now very soon
whatever amount we have, that
entire amount will be added to our account, whatever bank
account we have added, that money will be
added to our account, so many people were thinking
that after going cashless, will
we be able to apply for experiment and post
or not, so after that friends,
today you are going to know that
even after doing pre and post hospitalization, we
can apply here, for that,
friends, I have made today's video for you,
if you liked our video, then
you should like this video, share it
and subscribe to our channel
and whatever your friends are,
if you need information about this, then
before this I have made two more videos, so
you can get information about it by watching those videos also
and that was all for today,
thank you, that's it.